[Music]
most Filipinos worried worried for the
kids their future their homes worried
they might regret not living life to the
fullest because of that really because
of that they don't get to enjoy their
lives and just end up getting by no what
if what if what if those words were gone
and that they all went away because of
people like us like you like you like
you like you
that is FWD don't get me wrong FWD still
is an insurance company but we're not
your ordinary insurance company
insurance isn't only about money though
there's a lot of money here I'll give
you that cuz the insurance at least for
us is for having the guts having the
courage live in the moment and live in
the now we're securing your future by
protecting what's important flying Maiki
skydiving scuba diving rock climbing
you're covered no cash insurance is as
much about tomorrow as it is about today
today today insurance it suggest about
Commission hate that thinking insurance
is for the mission to make people people
people yeah ready ready ready ready to
do that is FWD as financial wealth
planners you may not be designing cars
building the next big high-rise or
painting the opals of this generation
but as financial wealth planners you
make them all of them possible heroes to
the everyday heroes that's who you are
with FWD helping Filipinos secure their
future fulfill their dreams while
fulfilling yours at your old base at
your own place no exaggerations doesn't
matter how much you've got right now
because you don't need capital doesn't
matter who you are why castle ohsaka
gakuen from the world of finance retail
Realty Pharma or even fashion you are
meant to be here WD doesn't matter if
you knew we're already in the world of
insurance
there's always room to grow and succeed
with us our training social support in a
category of its own here you'll find
what it takes to lead to innovate to
transform to really be successful as
successful as you want to be growth only
happen in a place that keeps on moving
forward meaning your growth truly begins
applicable unique so join us because
you're meant to live to thrive not just
survive join us because we get people
and we put them at the center every
appealable because we are fresh relevant
anesthetic when you sanjaya woman
because going paperless music forests
won't suffer for your success because
the future is digital and digital is FWD
join us trips in New York Geneva Russell
North Pole Paulina because there's no
greater heroism and bringing out the
hero in everyone join us so you can
change the way people feel about
insurance
we are the Philippines we are a shoe we
are FWD